Vonnegut, Bernard; Papers ua902.068
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Manuscripts, 1867-1997; Undated; 7; 8.57 cubic ft.
  - Gradient Measuring Device, 1962 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Huntsville, Alabama Tornadoes, 1966; 1974-1976 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18-19)
  - Inquiries on Possible Smithsonian Magazine Article, 1970-0 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Ice Nucleation Articles from Other Researchers, 1982-1983 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - IUGG XXI General Assembly (International Union of Geodesy and Geophysics), 1995 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Journal of Geophysical Research, Sweden, 1987-1989 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Kenster & Battista "Chemical and Physical Factors Affecting Mammalian Ciliary Activity", 1966 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Letter: "Cloud Formations", 1983 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Letter: Discussion of Paper by J. Brian Matthews, 1967-0 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Letter: Discussion of Paper by W. H. Evans, 1968-1969 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Letter: "Electrification of Frost Deposits", 1965 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Letter: "Increased Rates of Rainfall Production in Electrified Clouds", 1973 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Letter: "Laboratory Modeling of Cumulus Behavior in a Gaseous Medium", 1965 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Letter: "Nucleation and Lattice Disregistry", 1972 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Letter: "Penetration of Thunderstorm Anvils by Convective Cells", 1966 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Letter: Processes Causing Electrification of Ice Crystals in Thunderclouds", 1991-1992 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Letter: "Role of Cumulus Downdrafts in Stratosphere-Troposphere Exchange and in Cloud Electrification", 1996 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Letter: "Tornadoes: Puzzling Phenomena and Photographs", 1967 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Letters about Science Article on Toledo Tornado, 1966-1967 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Letter Discussing William R. Bennett Jr.'s Article, 1995 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Letter to the Editor: Allegiance to Theory Changes with the Wind", 1994 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Another Measurer of Rainfall Rate", 1996 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Ball Lightning Observation", 1975-1976 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Cloud-to-Stratosphere Lightning", 1979-1980 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Letter to the Editor: Comments on Science Weather Modification Article, 1978 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Comments on 'The ELDORA/ASTRAIA Airborne Doppler Weather Radar: High-Resolution Observations from TOGA COARE'", 1996 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Comment on 'Trip Illumines Lighting' by R.D. Hill", 1995 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Effect of Low Temperature on the Leakage of Charge from Irradicated Methyl Methacrylate Blocks", 1958 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 45)
  - Letter to the Editor: "The Electrification of Thunderstorms", 1989 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 46)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Importance of Electricity in Weather?", 1994-1996 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 47)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Jovian Lightning After Comet Impacts?", 1983; 1985; 1994-1995 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 48)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Lightning", 1972 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 49)
  - Letter to the Editor: Lightning - Observation from Space, 1979 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 50)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Lightning Strikes to Fresh Water", 1972; 1976 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 51)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Lightning Triggered at a Distance by Aircraft?", 1973 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 52)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Meteorological Phenomena Called Crown Flash", 1970-1972 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 53)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Penetration of Thunderstorm Anvils by Convective Cells", 1966 (Box 6 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 54)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Presters", 1913; 1959; 1991 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Reply to "Nucleation and Lattice Disregistry", 1972 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Thunderstorm Activity", 1973 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Thunderstorm Electrification", 1966 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Thunderstorm Electrification Mechanisms", 1988-1989 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Tornado Wind Speeds", 1975-0 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Vertical Lightning", 1983-1984 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - Letter to the Editor: "Weather and Climate Changes Arising from Solar Wind Effects on Thunderstorm Electrification", 1995 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - Lightning Strike, Mt. Evans, Colorado, 1971-1972 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Literature References, 1954; Undated (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - "Luminous Phenomena" Reprint Requests, 1966-1967; 1970 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - The Macmillan Company, 1969 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Madera Tornado Article, 1967 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Men and Molecules Script on Surtsey, 1968 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - MIT Icing Instructions, 1945 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Mitchell, Elias C.D., "How We Were Hit by the Tornado-Lightly", 1974 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Monograph: "Some Facts and Speculations Concerning the Origin and Role of Thunderstorm Electricity", 1963 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Monograph: "Some Facts and Speculations Concerning the Origin and Role of Thunderstorm Electricity", Undated (Oversized 4, Folder 21)
  - Natural History Press, 1968 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - NMIMT Data, 1952; 1954 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Nucleation Diagrams, 1974; Undated (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Observations from a U-2 of a Vortex Circulation in Clouds off the California Coast on October 1, 1962, 1962-1963 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Observations from "Early American Tornadoes 1586-1870" by David M. Ludlam, Undated (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Paper: "Aircraft-produced Ice Particles (APIPs) in Supercoded Clouds and the Probable Mechanism for their Production", 1991 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Paper: "Airborne Sferics Measurements", 1973 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Paper: "Airplane Smoke Trails as a Tool for the Study of Convective Clouds", 1958-1971 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Paper: "Atmospheric Electric Disturbances Produced by the Volcano at Surtsey, Iceland", 1964-1965 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Paper: "The Atmospheric Electricity Paradigm", 1993-1996 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27-28)
  - Paper: "The Effect of Screaming Layers on Laboratory and Natural Charged Clouds", 1967 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Paper: "Hollow Initial Radar Precipitation Echoes in New Mexico Thunderstorms", 1958 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Paper: "Lightning Detection from Satellites", 1974; 1976; 1978 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Paper: "Nucleation Catalysis", 1951-1952 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Paper: "Nucleation in the Martian Atmosphere", 1976 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Paper: "Possible Mechanism for Formation of Thunderstorm Electricity", 1953-1954; 1956; 1971 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Paper: "Review of 'Electric Potential Gradients Above Thunderstorms'", 1964; 1966; 1972 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Paper: "Supercooled Clouds", Undated (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Paper: "Thunderstorm and Lightning Observations from Space Shuttle", 1978-1979 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Paper: "Thunderstorm Electricity", 1962 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Paper: "Thunderstorm Theory", 1963-1964 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Paper: "Venusian Lightning- A Spectroscopic Study of Electrical Discharges in CO2 from Three to Sixty Atmospheres", 1981 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Paper: "Weather Modification and Air Pollution", 1967-1968 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - Papers, 1951-1957 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - Papers in Preparation, 1952-1977 (Box 7 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43-44)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Data, 1962 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 2)
  - Photographs from Space Charge Report, Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 3)
  - Pictures, Diagrams, 1955; 1958; Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 4)
  - Portfolio, 1954-1955 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 5)
  - Presentation: Clear Air Seeding, 1979; 1981 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 6)
  - Production of Miniature Whirlwinds in the Laboratory, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 7)
  - "Proposal to Make Measurements of Atmospheric Electrical Effects Produced by Kuwaiti Oil Fires", 1991 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 8)
  - "Proposed Legislation to Reduce Textbook Error", Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 9)
  - Remarks with John Latham, 1964-1965 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 10)
  - Reply to Comments on an Article by R.P. Davies-Jones and J.H. Golden, 1975 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 11)
  - Reply to Comments on "Importance of Including Time in the Specification of Ice Nuclei Concentrations", 1988 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 12)
  - Reports "Contractor Prepared on Technical Development and/or Operational Development Contracts", 1957 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 13)
  - Report: "Electrical Behavior of an Airplane in a Thunderstorm", 1965 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 14)
  - Report: "Investigation of the Practicability of Dissipating Natural Fog by means of Hygroscopic Material" MIT, 1937 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 15)
  - Report: Nighttime/Daytime Optical Survey of Lightning and Convective Phenomena Experiment (NOSL), 1979 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 16)
  - Report: "Preliminary Results to Determine Precedence of Electrification and Precipitation in Thunderstorms", 1957; Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 17)
  - Response to R.D. Hills Article in EOS, 1986 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 18)
  - Review: Atmospheric Electrodynamics, Hans Volland, 1984-1985 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 19)
  - Review: Atmospheric Electricity Vol. 2, H. Israel and H. Dolezalek, 1974-1975 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 20)
  - Review: Electrical Processes in Atmospheres, H. Dolezalek and R. Reiter, 1978 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 21)
  - Review: "Lightning and Its Spectrum," Leon E. Salanave, 1980-1981 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 22)
  - Review: "Lightning Chapter by Fuquay and Kasemir", 1972 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 23)
  - Review: The Earth's Electrical Environment, National Academy Press, 1986-1987 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 24)
  - Review: The Lightning Book, P.E. Viemietser, 1973; 1975 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 25)
  - Review: Understanding Lightning, Martin Uman, 1971 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 26)
  - Review of Articles by Ted Baker, 1945; Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 27)
  - Review: "Weather Modification by Cloud Seeding," Arnett Dennis, 1980; 1981 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 28)
  - Robbins, Janice and Charles "People are Storming over the Weather", 1971 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 29)
  - Science Books, 1961-1976 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 30)
  - Silver Iodide Demonstration, Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 31)
  - Silver Iodide Smoke, 1947-1950 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 32)
  - Stabilization of Vortex, 1971 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 33)
  - Stages of Cloud Conductivity, Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 34)
  - Sykes Letter in Weatherwise Asking Readers for Samples, 1967 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 35)
  - Teachers Guide to Atmospheric Electricity, 1971; 1973-1974 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 36)
  - Technical Paper: "Thunderstorm Overflight Program", 1980 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 37)
  - Technical Paper, 1951; 1962 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 38)
  - Technical Report No. SCL-2102-E, 1952-1953 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 39)
  - Thesis Materials- Robert Ryan, 1967; 1969; 1972-1973 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 40)
  - Thunderstorm Observations from Shuttle, 1975-1985; Undated (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 41)
  - UMSCHAU, 1966-1967; 1970; 1972 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 42)
  - University of Michigan Press Article, 1968 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 43)
  - Untitled Lightning Article, BME, 1976 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 44)
  - Untitled Rough draft, 1957-1958 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 45)
  - Water Fountain Diagram, 1954; 1964 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 46)
  - Weather Modification, 1969 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 47)
  - Weather Modification Association, 1977; 1985 (Box 8 (7-Manuscripts), Folder 48)
- State University of New York at Albany, 1957-1997; Undated; 8; 4.22 cubic ft.
  Series 8 documents the work that Dr. Vonnegut did while employed at SUNY Albany. During his time at SUNY Albany, Dr. Vonnegut taught classes, served on committees, attended conferences, and continued his research concerning weather, lightning, and clouds. Much of the research that Dr. Vonnegut did while at SUNY Albany was done as part of government research projects. Most notable was his work on Project Themis which was conducted by the United States Air Force. The project's main focus was on the modification and structure of clouds and fog but also investigated other areas of research such as raindrop dynamics and atmospheric electrical phenomena
  Included in this series are flyers, pamphlets, photographs, reports, project proposals, correspondence, travel arrangements, purchasing requests, conference programs, meeting agendas, press releases, newspaper and magazine clippings, handwritten notes, drawings, figures, and materials related to classes Dr. Vonnegut taught. Class materials include lists of students as well as tests and grades students received. Materials with personal information about students are restricted.
  - AFCRL Contracts, 1966-1974; 1976; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Air Force Proposal - Strobie, 1957; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Excellence in Research Awards, 1985 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 3)
  - American Meteorological Society Committee on Atmospheric Electricity, 1971-1976 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 4)
  - American Meteorological Society Committee on Cloud Physics, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 5)
  - American Meteorological Society - Outstanding Contribution Award, 1969; 1975-1976; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 6)
  - Army Research Institute, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 7)
  - Army Research Office, 1988; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 8)
  - Atmospheric Electricity Book List, Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 9)
  - Atmospheric Research Review Board, 1970-1972; 1975-1983; 1986 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 10)
  - Atmospheric Research Review Board, 1987-1992; 1994 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 11)
  - Atmospheric Research Review Board, Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 12)
  - Chaff Drop Exp. - Kropfli, 1979; 1987-1989 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 13)
  - Chaff Drop Exp. - Kropfli, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 14)
  - Committee on Promotions and Continuing Appointments at the College of Science and Mathematics, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 15)
  - Committee to Develop Doctor of Arts Program, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1996; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Conferences, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Department of Defense Scientific Research, 1974-1976 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Project Themis, 1967 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Project Themis, 1968 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Project Themis, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Project Themis, 1971-1974; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Strobie, 1975; 1983; 1989 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 24)
  - Response to R.D. Hills Article in EOS, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 25)
  - Council on Research, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 26)
  - Council on Research, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 27)
  - Course: ATM 407- Atmospheric Chemistry - [RESTRICTED], 1970-1971; 1973-1977; 1979-1983 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 28)
  - Course: ATM 407- Atmospheric Chemistry - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 29)
  - Course: ATM 518- Meteorological Instrumentation - [RESTRICTED], 1974; 1976; Undated (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 30)
  - Course: ATM 518- Meteorological Instrumentation - [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 31)
  - Course: ATM 524: Atmospheric Electricity Taught with Dr. Ornik - [RESTRICTED], 1969-1977 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 32)
  - Course: ATM 524: Atmospheric Electricity 1 - [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 33)
  - Course: ATM 524 - Atmospheric Electricity 1 - [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 34)
  - Course: ATM 524 - Atmospheric Electricity 1 - [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 35)
  - Course: PHYS 534 - Cloud Physics, 1980 (Box 1 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 36)
  - Course Materials - [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Course Rosters - [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
  - Dept. of Energy Basic Energy Services Program Assessment Committtee, 1981 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 3)
  - Distinguished Professor, 1983-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 4)
  - External Reviewer: UMIST - Colin John Stevens, 1983; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 5)
  - First SUNY Albany ONR Grant 20-6016A, 1967-1973 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 6)
  - General Motors Res Lab - W.G. Agnew, 1989; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 7)
  - General Committee Correspondence, 1967-1972; 1974; 1976; 1979 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 8)
  - General Committee Correspondence, Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 9)
  - Graduate Academic Council, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 10)
  - Grant - "The Electrical Effects of Lightning on Thundercloud Precipitation Development", 1972; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 11)
  - Grant - "Investigation of Maritime Thunderstorms", 1971-1977; 1990 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 12)
  - Grant - "Investigation of Maritime Thunderstorms", Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 13)
  - Grant - NASA - 32893 Observations of Lightning from Space, 1980-1986 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 14)
  - Grant - NASA 40-OPPI-76-1 "Nighttime and Daylight Optical Survey of Thunderstorm Lightning and Convective Behavior to be Conducted During the Oft Shuttle Flight Program", 1976-1982 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 15)
  - Grant - NASA NAG 8-628 "Observations of Thunderstorms from U-2 Airplane", 1983-1990 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 16)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation I034732- 001 "Development of Cloud Seeding Technology Utilizing Modified Silver Iodide Structures", 1972-1975 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 17)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation 8419112 "Electrical Processes in the Upper Cloud-Air Interface", 1988-1990; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 18)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation A036100 "Vortex Stabilized High Voltage Discharge" - [RESTRICTED], 1970-1977 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 19)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation A041166 "The Electrical Properties of Snowstorms", 1973-1976 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 20)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation A041184 "Meteorological Effects Produced by Niagara Falls" - [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 21)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM 7600908 "Atmospheric Electricity" - [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 22)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM 7600908 "Atmospheric Electricity" - [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 23)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM 7921080 "Atmospheric Electricity" - [RESTRICTED], 1979-1984 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 24)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM-7921080 "Atmospheric Electricity", 1985 (Oversized 3, Folder 21)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM- 7921080 "Atmospheric Electricity" - [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 25)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation ATM 8419112 "Electrical Processes in Upper Cloud Air Interface", 1958; 1964; 1971; 1983-1987 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 26)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation DES 74-18286 "The Nature of Lightning Initiation", 1974-1977 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 27)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation GA-1017 "Behavior of Electrified Atmospheric Particles During Phase Change" - [RESTRICTED], 1966-1974 (Box 2 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 28)
  - Grant - National Science Foundation GA 28047 "Vortex Stabilized High Voltage Discharge", 1970-1972 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 1)
  - Grant - ONR "Atmospheric Physical Studies" - [RESTRICTED], 1982-1987 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 2)
  - Grant - ONR "Microphysical Studies of Noctilucent Clouds", 1980; 1984-1986 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 3)
  - Grant - "A Study Stratospheric Discharges", 1974-1975; 1977-1978 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 4)
  - Grant - "A Study Stratospheric Discharges", 1979-1981 (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 5)
  - Grant - "A Study Stratospheric Discharges", Undated (Box 3 (8-State University of New York at Albany), Folder 6)